[music]
>> What's up turtle gang? This is our last
stop in New York, Sweetgreen. Already
ingested.
Now we're going to JFK.
Check this out. I had one kiwi [music]
left.
Symbolic.
Should I eat it now?
>> [music]
>> A little sour,
but I'm going to finish it. Let's go to
the airport, shall we?
First time wearing my hiking boots in
too long,
>> [music]
>> and it feels funny to wear them on the
streets of New York.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yo.
We made it here to Auckland, and then we
fly direct to Christchurch. So by the
time we land there, it will have been
Oh, I'll add it up and put it on the
screen right here. [music]
It's a lot of hours. Feeling good,
weather's nice, 60s. My feet are a
little sweaty cuz the hiking boots.
That's all right. And I can't stop from
imitating the accent.
>> [music]
[music]
>> What's up, turtle gang? We got our
rental car. I don't know why I'm doing
this. Completely delusional, no sleep. I
don't know how long now, but we got our
rental car.
And uh
Let's drive into the town, shall we?
[music]
My companion on the way here absolutely
crushed it. We're driving on the left
side of the road. [music] I'm a little
afraid to do it when my time comes.
Half cold, half warm. That's my
solution.
How idyllic [music] is this? So very
idyllic.
>> [music]
>> Don't mind if we do.
All right, with all those [music]
options in there, I selected momo.
Throwback Jackson Heights video. This is
a Nepalese dish with a It's got like a
[music] tomato-y sesame soup base with
uh chicken momo. Someone told me in a
video momo is plural without the S. It's
just momo. So, now I [music] know. And I
got a mango lassi, which I drank in
minute and a half, I would say. And
finished off with a dessert.
Okay, at this point, after 32 hours of
travel and about 5 more hours walking
around in Christchurch, we were so
[music] incredibly exhausted and
delirious. But, we kept ourselves awake
and moving just long enough to go to
sleep at a reasonable [music] time to
try to get on the new time zone. Also
guys, I know this is a long video, my
longest ever, but if there's any video
where I would say that it's absolutely
worth it to watch until the end, it is
this one. With each day, the scenery
just gets more beautiful and surreal.
So, stick with it, watch it like a
little movie, and I hope you love it.
Be the cat
>> [music]
>> in the sun. All right, morning number
two. We're going to this place for
brunch. Look at this parallel park that
my companion just accomplished. First
breaky,
>> [music]
>> 10 out of 10. The smoked salmon, egg, we
got seasonal fruits, which of course
includes kiwis and cherries. Be happy
about it. Look at all the plants.
This place could so easily be in
Southern California, we were talking
about. Great vibe. And now, driving to
Lake Tekapo.
It's safe to say the best way to see New
Zealand [music] is by road tripping. You
drive through so many different types of
scenery, and time on the road blasting
The Strokes [music] and Tame Impala and
tons of New Zealand based artists was a
highlight in itself [music] for us.
Lake Tekapo. Its color looks absolutely
fake. So, we're walking over to the
Church of the Good [music] Shepherd
Church, which is a hot spot for
photographers and tourists in general.
It's really beautiful.
>> [music]
>> Okay, so these purple flowers are more
so in season or in blooms [music] until
like late December, but we're lucky.
They're not as like vibrant as usual,
but we still have remnants. Wow,
stunning.
>> [music]
>> Rainy hike. [music]
What's up Turtle Gang?
Here we are
on a rainy hike. We thought, should we
stay inside, watch Lord of the Rings?
Nope. We came out hiking anyway. What,
like an hour ago we started probably?
Pretty steady uphill, and then at the
top it's going to be a nice view of the
lake. Shall we carry on?
We made it!
This visibility is a little murky, but
Okay, this is one thing about New
Zealand. You are at the mercy of its
ever-changing weather. By and large, we
got extremely lucky most days [music] as
you'll see, but some days like this one,
you just have to submit. It was a bummer
because this is the McKenzie region in
New Zealand, which is home to some of
the darkest skies in the world, which
means some of the brightest stars that
you'll ever see, but not with cloud
cover. Even so, we ended the night in a
hot tub in misty weather, and who knows,
maybe just maybe at the end of our trip
we might circle back to this area and
have beautiful weather. I guess we'll
have to wait and see.
>> [music]
[music]
>> After 2 and 1/2 hours of a beautiful
drive, we made it to Wanaka [music] and
got the sun back. We were honestly
feeling the jet lag pretty heavily and
trying to keep ourselves as active as
possible, so we set out on a nice long
bike ride around Lake Wanaka. On a bike
ride. [music]
Little did we know this town would end
up becoming one of our favorite spots
[music] in the whole world.
>> We are biking here Lake Wanaka.
Wanaka. Okay, so we're basically on a 20
km loop around the lake, around the edge
of the lake and then through the town
again. So, yeah, 2 2 and 1/2 hours. They
didn't have any more e-bikes for the
day, so we're doing
>> [music]
>> analog, baby. Quad day, baby.
Oh, yeah. All right, check back in in a
bit.
>> [music]
>> Hello.
This is Taylor. We just finished a 15-mi
bike ride. It was the prettiest bike
ride I've ever done. Probably the number
one highlight was one of the cutest
Cavalier King Charles Spaniels I've ever
seen on the trail [music] as we were
biking. My companion here was up ahead
of me a little bit. When he came upon
the guy with the cav, he said, "You're
about to have the world's biggest fan in
just a second." And as I rolled up, I
was
It was one of the cutest ones we've both
of us have ever seen. And then I said,
"Oh my gosh, can I pet him?" He's like,
"Yeah." Takes the dog,
puts him in my arms.
>> played with him for like 10 minutes, and
it was actually one of the cutest cats
in the entire world. Mine would be very
jealous, but they're on the other side
of the world, so they don't need to
know. And now we're back in Wanaka and
walking around. One of our goals for
this
>> [music]
>> trip is each day we want to maximize
end-of-day exhaustion levels, so that
way we're just super sleepy by the end
of the night, get really good sleep, and
ready to go the next day. I would say
we've already hit the EOD exhaustion
[music] meter for today. We're doing a
little a little more walk along the
lake.
>> [music]
[music]
>> How cool is this? My companion found
this. Is it an independent movie
theater? Inside they have food named
after movies, and then something that
we're going to do is called real fruit
[music] ice cream, where I guess they
just mix like berries and actual fruit
with vanilla ice cream and a machine.
Seems simple, but I'm excited to try.
All right, past dinner,
we're staying on the ice cream grind.
Anyway, Black Peak is obviously the spot
in town. But, Hokey Pokey, this is the
flavor that we got in Christchurch.
Yeah, it's like kind of vanilla with
honeycomb pieces, and it looks like this
There's a little chocolate, too. I don't
know if it's a New Zealand thing, an
Aussie thing, this part of the world
thing. Delicious. Oh, and cone culture
is also huge. I don't see any cups. No
one's eating it out of cups. So, we're
just going to walk around a little bit.
Obviously, the sun goes down really late
this time of year, which is super nice.
Over and out.
>> [music]
>> I got a bathing suit.
Sports bra,
companion's underwear.
Very refreshing. Very cold.
On our way [music] to Rob Roy Glacier
track.
We had a lovely breakfast. The nicest
subscriber in the entire world, who I
hope is watching this. He walked in and
we talked for a little bit. We had a
huge breakfast. We each ordered like
four things because the prices are great
when you convert it to New York dollars
anyway. And we talked to the the people
working there and they told us their
favorite hiking recommendations. And
then we talked to people who are also
tourists and they validated their
decisions. So, anyway.
This is the life, baby. I was doing this
and my companion walked out and couldn't
locate me because he didn't clock my
lifeless body as a as a human being
laying here, much less his companion.
So, we got our Americanos.
We just thought Oh, I like this song.
We're on our way to Rob Roy Glacier.
Both of us just wanted another little
coffee and so we stopped here. This
really, really cute little cafe, kind of
in the middle of nowhere, but look at
the surroundings. [music]
Excellent.
>> [music]
>> All right. We have begun Rob Roy Glacier
track, [music] baby.
Come join.
>> [music]
>> This is so cool.
Here's a bread truck.
How cool is this bridge?
We're entering another biome. After
crossing the bridge, it turns totally
foresty. Smells so good.
We're climbing.
>> [music]
>> This was our first big hike of the trip.
My companion and I commented many times
on this hike how happy we were just
[music] to be spending this time
outdoors with the sun on our skin,
swapping New York winter for New [music]
Zealand summer.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Wow, wow, wow. What do we have here?
Hello, it's Portal Day. We are exhausted
from that hike, [music] but we got back
to town, had a really yummy dinner, and
we got our real fruit ice cream. You'd
think we would stop with activities, but
no, no, we have a really fun activity
tonight. Oh, I also have to say our
whole plan, yes, we had an itinerary and
an idea of what [music] we wanted to do,
but pretty much everything that we've
done has been at the recommendation of
just a really nice Kiwi that we've met.
Everyone's been so, so nice, so helpful.
Love you, Kiwis.
You're awesome.
in
>> [music]
>> my boyfriend's underwear.
I mean, my companion.
>> [laughter]
>> Woo!
The Secret Sauna felt like a local
hidden gem that we somehow stumbled
into. The scalding heat, the freezing
[music] lake, the mix of travelers and
locals who had lived there for years. We
went back and forth between the heat and
the cold until I lost track of time
[music] completely. And by the end, I
was that kind of tired that that get as
a little kid from being outside all day
doing nothing but having fun.
What's up, turtle gang? Here we are at
yet another delicious breakfast. I
ordered salmon on my toast, and I
thought it was going to be like a thin
layer of smoked salmon. I got a whole
fillet for $6. Anyways, another full day
here in Wanaka before we do a bungee
jumping sound.
Another day, another hike.
>> [music]
>> What's up, T-gang?
Finished our little hike, came back to
Wanaka for coffee and bagels. Can't stay
away from New York for too long.
>> But this is just cutest area. Look, it's
kind of like food trucks in this little
oasis where the river runs through.
Adorable. Now we have some more outdoor
fun things to come, but like on the
chill side, which I think we're looking
forward to after yesterday's hike.
Really good. Nice and soft, just how I
like it. Nice and soft? No, what?
Oh, yeah, baby.
>> [music]
>> What up, T's? T-gang.
Uh, it's been fun and all, but about an
hour ago, we went on a 4-point It ended
up being like 4.5 mile run. I'm gassed,
or I was gassed. And so now we're here
at Rhyme and Reason, which is one of the
top breweries that's been recommended to
us by locals. It's cool. Take a
look-see. [music] Big old distillery
vats and all that good stuff. I got a
New Zealand pilsner, which I also was
recommended. Pilsners in New Zealand are
a bit hoppier than ones that you would
get in the US and Europe. And they're
true. Very refreshing and delicious. But
also just such a good vibe. We're going
to go to a couple of different
breweries. We've been doing a pretty
good 50/50 balance of like pretty hard
physical activity, and then treating
ourselves accordingly between beer, Tim
Tams, good food, and I like it.
Signing off. Hello.
Or should I say hello?
How fitting. Got it.
>> We are now at Ground Up Brewing.
>> This is the second brewery and it's just
literally right next to Rhine and Reason
over there. This one also came highly
recommended and this one is cider
logger. We'll see how it is.
>> [music]
>> It's good. Can I try yours, too?
Mhm.
This is fun. I like them both. See the
distillery? Pretty neat.
Last breakfast [music] in Wanaka before
driving to Queenstown.
Kind of sad, but excited. Over the next
few days, we're kind of just mapping
[music] out what we want to do since we
have basically thrown our itinerary out
the window. So, that's what we're
talking about. Till then, delish
brekkie. I think both of us want to eat
a little bit
cleaner for a couple days. We've been
having a lot of Tim Tams.
>> [music]
>> I keep forgetting to film these things
because they're just so casually on the
side of the road everywhere, but
everywhere is super cute. Cool general
store. And then we got into a
conversation with a Kiwi, as we do, and
got lots of recommendations for
Queenstown. So, let's go.
A bit about where we're heading.
Queenstown [music] is known as the
adventure capital of the world, where
modern bungee jumping was founded and
all other adventure and adrenaline
[music] junkie activities that you can
possibly think of are readily available.
Not to mention the sheer beauty of the
town itself, [music]
nestled into mountains with a big lake
at its center. We made it to Queenstown.
Aw.
And I found a pooch.
Aw, so sweet. Hey pooch.
>> [music]
>> We settled in. We rerouted our itinerary
for the next few days. Oh boy, do we
have a treat coming up. And now, today's
a pretty easy day. Recalibrating before
we begin the bigger hikes and the views
and all that. I guess uh first
impressions perhaps of Queenstown. A lot
of people told us that it's really
really touristy, but just very crowded.
And I kind of figured [music] by our
standards in New York, like how crowded
is it really? And as we were driving
through it, it was pretty crowded. I
think it was more crowded than we were
expecting, but beyond beautiful. Like
this is just the view of the surrounding
area. We're about to go walk. I will say
though, Wanaka is hard to beat. No one's
making me choose, but I feel like I
should.
All right.
See you soon.
This is just [music] in the center of
the city. Also, if it looks like my
mascara's running, it's because
he did something funny. I was crying
laughing for what, 5 whole minutes?
Casual view.
>> [laughter]
>> I always approach the camera really
aggressively. Casual view. This is
literally in the center [music]
of Queenstown. This is Queenstown Garden
Trail. Just an easy like 25-minute walk
around this little peninsula. I'll show
you on the map, and then we're going to
walk into town and go from there.
Very accessible alpine biome.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I already had some bites, so you're not
getting the first reaction. This is
insane. I got a regular chocolate chip
cookie.
>> [music]
>> I got a cup of milk, and then I got this
little s'more chocolate chip cookie
[music] s'more with melted chocolate. We
were just saying, restaurants overthink
dessert. This is better than anything
you will get in a restaurant. Like any
fancy dessert, [music]
uh-uh. This is as good as it gets. We
will be back.
>> [music]
>> Crazy. I was just about to hop in the
shower [music] for the night, and then I
looked out the window and I thought I
saw this color light, and I'm glad I
came [music] out to check.
Wow.
>> [music]
>> Good morning. We made it to Arrowtown,
which is just a 20-minute drive outside
of Queenstown. Honestly, it's way cuter
than I was expecting. I think [music]
it's because we sat down at the coffee
shop and talked to locals who live here.
It's kind of cool. Like you'd think it
would just be a tourist trap, [music]
but the locals were down here drinking
coffee, so that's a good sign. Anyways,
look at it.
>> [music]
>> So now about to start a day of more
hiking, more activities, banana, coffee,
and water. [music]
Join.
Beautiful hike, but then we have an
Alaskan bull worm.
>> [music]
>> Oh, maybe show the lupins.
Woo.
Great break. Headed back to Arrowtown
after our It'll be about an hour total
loop. Super chill, but just nice to move
the blood a little bit. All right. The
cherries are a big thing here in New
Zealand. I just bought a whole bag of
them. If you can name the other video
where I just bought a bag of cherries
for the day,
let me know in the comments. They also
are making the real fruit ice cream over
there. For strawberries and cherries.
But we have lunch ahead of us, so I just
got the the cherries. Delicious.
All right. Leaving Arrowtown for lunch.
We're going to Amisfield Wines and
Artisan [music] Kitchen. Found both of
these places, sounded good.
And then more activities ahead. Come
with me.
Hello.
Hello. We made it to Amisfield Wines and
Artisan Kitchen. Insanely beautiful.
It's fancier than we thought. [music]
Look at this butter.
You ever seen butter served on a rock
like that? Bet not.
Oh, it's truffle.
It's truffle [music] butter.
Delicious.
Heading up this absolute serpentine road
[music] to The Remarkables Lookout,
which during the winter is a ski slope
and during the summer home to stunning
lookouts and hikes. However, we were not
prepared for what was to come.
>> [music]
>> Lake Alta, honestly, do not recommend in
this weather.
But, pretty cool. We are very high
[music] up. Here's the peak and then
here's sort of the prettiest view. Well,
in all honesty, we went the wrong way.
We went up I don't even know how many
feet of elevation we went up, but
came up to the top of a ski lift. We
walked it. I'm feeling it. At least we
saw the lake.
Here we go.
This looks pretty cool cuz it's all
glass. Stunning.
Absolutely stunning. Well,
should we see you guys at the top?
>> [music]
>> Second day in a row, baby. I'm back
today. I just got two s'mores. [music] I
already drank the milk. Double down on
the good thing, you know.
>> [music]
>> Our laundry drying solution since they
didn't come totally dry in the Airbnb
dryer. Uh, creative. Hello.
I said it wrong. [laughter]
Hello. Last morning in Queenstown
[music]
and the forecast called for a little
rain. Do you see rain? Look at that.
It's actually kind of the most beautiful
morning or like the most amount of sun
that we've had in Queenstown [music] so
far. And then look at this cute little
coffee, little bullet coffee food truck
[music] thingy. We're going to go get
one.
A coffee there after breakfast. I can't
get over how pretty it is.
>> [music]
>> Didn't get any footage of breakfast, but
it was good. And now, as promised, a
coffee at this little place. It's so
cute. Okay, we thought we should do at
least one of these adrenaline-y
activities while in Queenstown, so we
chose one and then had a couple hours to
kill before doing it. So, we headed to
Bob's Cove.
>> [music]
>> Oh, hello. Bob's Cove, baby. Look look,
absolutely [music] stunning as you can
see by all the bikini-clad women and
swim trunk-clad men. I'm dressed
appropriately for the occasion. That's
all right. Digestives, [music]
delicious. Look how clear. Can you tell
how clear it is?
Beautiful. Oh yeah, baby. And then our
chosen adrenaline activity awaited
[music] us.
>> [music]
>> All right, here we go.
That's what I'm about to fly.
A little cute, a little nervous, but in
a good way. Just like slight [music]
butterflies. What a perfect
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey guys. So,
there's an incident I have to tell you
about. It happened about 30 minutes ago.
So, we went paragliding as you saw and
we started doing some tricks, which I
wanted to do. Like, you know, where you
go back and forth and you really start
pulling some G's. And in the moment they
felt fun. I enjoyed it. And then [music]
upon landing, about 5 minutes after
that, I was like, "I don't know if I'm
feeling too hot." Anyways, we land not
feeling my best, but I'm like, "Ah,
it'll probably go away." And then about
a 20-minute drive back from where we
landed to Queenstown. I was sitting up
front with the driver knowing that I
wasn't feeling too hot. I was like,
"This isn't getting better." And so,
finally I just asked him to pull over.
So, we pulled over to a very picturesque
spot and I threw up all the contents
[music] inside my body. Most of which
were cherries. And so,
you can imagine that how you how you
must. And now I'm drinking a peach
ginger sparkling water. But yeah, I just
thought you guys should know what
happened.
It was [music] honestly really, really,
really fun. I don't know. I've done
crazy aerobatic flights with my dad
before [music] and I'm a huge roller
coaster person. Yeah, the things that I
enjoy doing does not mesh well with my
motion sickness. Still think it was
worth it. Maybe the tricks I shouldn't
have done, but it was really fun while
we were doing it.
>> [music]
>> All right, for 2 days in a row now, this
has been our favorite place. Yum Hut,
it's called. It's a selection of food
trucks. [music]
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
This place was highly recommended. They
had it in Wanaka, too. And oh my god, I
got a scoop of hokey pokey covered in
Oh, it's messy. And milk chocolate.
Okay, I have to eat it now.
Okay, we're leaving Queenstown [music]
for the next location. And we're sitting
here reflecting on Queenstown compared
to other places we've been. And we just
said that in terms of like sheer beauty
of a city, Queenstown is
as beautiful as it could possibly get.
Just the houses and everything nestled
up in the hills [music]
of this like crazy
lake and mountain alpine environment. I
mean, it almost looks fake from pretty
much every single angle. However, Wanaka
still is [music] our favorite. I think
that we both liked the small town vibe
of Wanaka and it really didn't feel
too touristy. [music] Woke up, went to
the same cafe a couple times, made
friends with the baristas, and then
would run into the baristas in town
later that night. And you know, she gave
us recommendations [music] in the
morning and then she would ask us later
in the afternoon, like, "Oh, did you go
on that hike?" And it it felt like a
community, I think. [music] Versus
Queenstown was one just way more
touristy. Like there were quite a few
people. [music] I mean, we're tourists,
so it's it's not like tourism is bad in
and of itself, but the vibe just felt a
little bit fratty is the word that we
kept using. It kind of felt like a good
place for [music] a bachelor party is
one way we could describe it. It
definitely had some gems. I think that
today especially with the perfect
weather, it really rounded out
Queenstown in a nice way for us. But if
we had to choose, I think Wanaka's our
favorite.
>> [music]
>> Howdy.
We are up right and early.
Got a car now. The drive up to Milford
Sound is [music] supposed to be one of
the absolute most stunning in the entire
country. So,
I'll show it to you.
>> [music]
[music]
[singing]
>> We made it.
And this is the view just from the
parking lot. [music] Crazy. And then
back there, too.
It also just smells so fresh. I'm a big
smell person,
>> [music]
>> and it just smells like tree purified
air, if that makes sense. All right, so
you have about a 10-minute walk to the
beginning of uh
where we take the boat out.
>> [music]
[singing]
[music and singing]
[music]
>> We just happened to have this was the
first view that the first Europeans saw
and discovered Milford Sound. It's a
Welshman. For obvious reasons, [music]
Milford Sound is widely regarded as the
number one attraction in New Zealand.
And even [music] with that tagline, it
was still more serene than I'd expected.
It's one of the wettest places on Earth
with rain roughly 182 days of the year.
And somehow we got nothing but bright
[music] blue sunny skies. Funny enough,
locals say that it's most beautiful when
it's raining since that's what feeds
these waterfalls. Hundreds of little
streams that almost look like veins
running [music] down the rock face when
it's raining. But honestly, I couldn't
feel bad about the sunshine. Post
Milford Sound cruise lunch, quite the
local, and after this little carb load,
we're going to [music] head to a cool
hike.
Pretty good, too.
Switchbacks.
Woo! Heart pounding.
I'm feeling good.
Well, howdy there.
We're about 30 minutes from the top, but
little scenic lookout point. Had to show
you guys. Feeling good these switchbacks
[music] are helping the body get up and
it's pretty beautiful. And we're at high
elevation.
I should note. Let's carry on. [music]
>> [music]
>> So pretty.
It's the craziest [music] view.
Also,
lest we not forget, we're on top of the
mountain and she's like a plateau
[music] up here, but it feels like we're
on a flat.
>> [music]
>> Uh
crazy. I think that this is the biggest
bang for buck
hike that we've [music] done in New
Zealand, in my opinion.
What else are we going to do is what we
bark.
We were saying this has so many
different biomes. [music] New Zealand in
general, but this hike alone, up on this
plateau, if you're not looking over
there, it feels
>> [music]
>> borderline deserty. And then when you
look at some of these trees, it feels
tropical, kind of like you're in Hawaii.
And then you look at the mountains, it's
totally alpine. And then there's
glaciers over there, too. [music] So,
you kind of get a little bit of
everything. It's crazy.
>> [music]
>> Best post-hike snack, treat, I should
say. If you guys remember in my Trader
Joe's video, I talked about the Aussie
style biscuits being
my favorite thing ever, this is the real
version. And they do sell them in the US
in certain markets, but I'm just happy
to be buying them in this part of the
world.
>> [music]
>> Delish.
Oh, yeah.
Fish and chips to finish off the day.
What a vibe. Also, we're in Anau now,
which is the entrance to Fiordland. So,
I bet a lot of these people didn't know
for sure it's Te Anau today, too. And
our cute little Airbnb for the night.
And Manapouri, which is like a 15-minute
drive outside Te Anau. And yeah, you
can't hear anything but the sound of
rustling trees,
birds. It's pretty nice. We just went on
a little evening walk. We're pretty
shot, had to force ourselves to get out
for a little while before calling it a
night. And the sun goes down super late,
so you feel like the pressure to be up
[music] later than you definitely than
you do in New York,
>> [laughter]
>> during the winter, anyway. And then
tomorrow,
I guess we'll have to wait and see.
We're [music] going to a place that we
really, really like.
And on our little walk,
a honey
>> [music]
>> for sale station. We don't have cash on
us, but
how cool. Manuka honey, $10.
Wow. High trust.
First stop [music] in the morning. We've
really been enjoying our little morning
coffee runs, because you see stuff like
this on the side of the road all the
time. And we're in the middle of not too
much, [music] on our way up to Wanaka
today.
>> [music]
>> All right, we're back in Wanaka and
taking kind of a chill day today before
another full day tomorrow.
And so we came to another brewery.
There's a bunch of them just right here
in Wanaka. Like there's three or four
main ones. Lots of good spots. And so we
came here and I got another New Zealand
Pilsner. Let's see how it is.
Wow.
Looks good.
Well, it's my favorite one that we've
had so far. All right. My companion got
the Wanaka Lager.
Also good. They have a lot of like
flavor. I don't know what words to use
to describe it, but good vibes.
Oh, and another fun thing later on. So
we're still having a fun day. Playing
Bob Dylan.
Bob's.
Less than 20 minutes ago,
>> [music]
>> my companion and I were playing trivia
and I asked him, "What's my favorite
fruit?" And he said, "Besides tomato?"
And I said, "Yeah." He said,
"Nectarine?" [music]
I said, "Yeah." Then we come here for
dinner and there's a dish that is tomato
and nectarines. It's not a very likely
[music] combo to start with and the fact
that we just talked about it, crazy.
Flounder [music]
and more real fruit ice cream
for dessert. And we came back here.
>> [music]
[music]
>> So nice. Going between the sauna and the
lake and it's raining a little bit.
It's pretty insane. [music]
And back at our Airbnb. Still some nice
orange [music] glow in the sky. Road is
wet cuz it rained, but now it's dry. We
were just saying we keep getting so
lucky.
Oh, no!
If I took one thing away from how we
planned this trip, it's the value of
building in [music] real flexibility. We
had a handful of non-negotiables,
Milford Sound, Queenstown, and others.
But beyond those, we left a lot of days
open to stay longer where we wanted to
stay [music] longer, to let the weather
decide rather than fight it. When we saw
Mount Cook was going to be rainy and
gray, we realized that we were forcing
something [music] that didn't want to be
forced. And when a trip starts to feel
like friction, that's usually a sign.
So, we went back to our favorite place,
Wanaka. I think sometimes the best
travel decision is just to win more of
what you already love.
Oh, yeah, baby. Another day, another
bike ride. This time we got e-bikes
for comfort. We're biking from Lake
Wanaka to Lake Hawea. This is actually a
bike ride that we had on our original
itinerary. So, cool that [music] we're
doing it.
>> [singing]
>> I have to um sunscreen up, but
sheer beauty.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Oh, my goodness.
>> [music]
>> I'm not sure the camera's picking up how
blue the water is, but it's completely
like turquoise almost and completely
clear. And so, Secret Sauna, where we
were the other day, is [music] just up
the bay here. But we're going to go the
other way
today. Howdy.
Little break at [music] Hawea Hotel
with that view. We got a Earl Grey
kombucha as a little refreshment,
delicious, Wow, look at that.
Here we are. Just [music] finished the
bike ride. Hands are still filthy, but
we can finish what's on our list. So,
I'm scared here. It's closing in less
than 1 hour and we booked to here. We're
going to get a nice glass of sparkly
something something
with this view.
We ended up drinking Rippon because we
had to buy a bottle and they couldn't
open it for us there and we wanted just
a glass.
>> [music]
>> So, we came here to Verb which is back
in town. This has been one of the most
highly recommended spots by all the
locals that we've [music] talked to and
it's known for its wine but then also
its flowers which I didn't know until
now. So, every single table has like I
think these are dahlias like a stunning
little bouquet. That's nuts.
>> [music]
>> Got a little rosé.
Refreshing.
We had dinner.
>> [music]
>> I didn't film it, but we're back at the
movie theater with the real fruit ice
cream. Can I try yours?
>> [music]
>> That Wanaka Tree probably Wanaka's most
famous attraction.
Smaller than I thought it would be
actually. Look at all the people. Look
at all the tourist attraction. Us
included. All right, should we go read
the placards so we know how old it is
and stuff? Okay, that Wanaka Tree is
over 80 years old and some estimates
[music] putting it at around 100 years
old. It originated as a willow fence
post
>> [music]
>> which I don't know where that would be
have been, but it took root in the water
as you can see.
Which is pretty pretty cool. That's what
I learned. Oh, look there's a bird in
it. Here, I got I'll go [music] go and
show the bird.
>> [music]
>> All right, we are at Red Bread Berrries
on another beautiful day in Wanaka
[music] and we're going to go strawberry
picking.
Let's [music] find it. Oh, this one's
good and juicy. Oh, that's a nice one
right on all sides. Oh, yeah. Tempting
to not eat them right now. I think that
like kind of hidden ones are extra
[music] juicy and red, you know? Look at
that.
Perfect. Perfection. I mean, truthfully
they're all
just such good catches, but we're like,
"Oh, yeah, we're pretty [music] good at
this."
Look at our loot.
That's a big loot and this only took us
what? 5 minutes?
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, they're all perfect, too. Red all
the way around. That's a good one. Wow.
And then we're getting a bunch of
babies, too.
Little one-biters. This is fun. Quick.
Quicker than I thought.
>> Perhaps. Let's get a look. Yep, I'd say
so.
Okay, I think we're done. We're going to
eat these in [music] a day and a half.
About to go to the bathroom
next to some friends.
Finished [music] picking our
strawberries and then we went in there
and talked to the girl working here who
is also named Taylor. He's [music]
wearing the same aura ring and t-shirt
as me. We have a lot in common. And they
do real fruit ice cream here, [music]
obviously. But this is actually frozen
yogurt since we've done ice cream the
last however many days. Trying something
different.
>> Mhm.
Ooh, that is good. [music] It's more
tart like you said and it's more fruity.
They put more strawberries in it.
All right, here we are at the lavender
farms. We're kind of making our rounds
on the chill Wanaka [music] activities
before before our trip is done. So,
we're here. Lavender shop, honey
tasting, tea room, ice cream.
>> [music]
>> I'll walk around, enjoy. Maybe we'll get
a little lavender essential oil or
something for our shower because I did
that in the sauna the other day [music]
and I loved how it smelled. Anyway,
let's go on in. Already smells insane.
>> [music]
>> Got on some [music] lavender lip balms
and it's not overbearing actually. It
just smells really, really refreshing.
But we got tickets. We're going to go
out to the farm [music] after I've
doused myself in all the lavender
products. We're trying the honey here.
[music]
Ooh, that's good. This one's like a rich
tasting honey. Some of these other ones
are a little floral, like the lavender
one naturally. Just tried every single
one. This one is my favorite, product of
honey.
Oh my god, the flowers, too. Like
obviously the lavender, [music]
but there's just such beautiful flowers
everywhere. I don't know what they
harvest with a ton [music] of honey,
too. It's a lot of bees on lavender.
The color dahlias everywhere. [music]
I think they're dahlias. They sure look
like it.
>> [music]
>> Hello. All right, here we are in the
lavender [music] fields now. First of
all, the lavender is stunning, but I am
beyond impressed by New Zealand's flower
game. We're finding [music] New Zealand
is peaking really high on little
experiences like this, and then the
flower or the um strawberry picking that
we were just at, where [music] it's sort
of like you show up, choose your own
adventure, you buy a ticket, you go do
your thing. A lot of like wondering
experiences. [music]
With the strawberry fields, we showed
up, didn't have to like book anything.
They just say, "Oh, you want to pick?"
They're like, "Yeah." We're picking 2
seconds [music] later. Kind of the same
thing here. You can just wander and do
your own thing, which I really, really
like. All right, so this is cool. Here
are some of the bee boxes. I'm sure
there's a [music] better word for that,
but this is where they're doing the
thing. And then it's just a cool
ecosystem because they're there, and
then they pollinate
all of this.
>> [music]
>> Howdy. So off to the corner of
the lavender fields is this tree.
And I noticed these fruit, and I was
like, I got to see what what's going on.
So I picked one up off the ground, and
it's plum, a plum tree, [music] and
they're really good. The first bite that
we had was pretty tart, but these dark
red ones are that have fallen
so good. Mmm. This one looks pretty
good.
Mmm, a little tart.
Delicious, though.
And so we embarked our final [music]
long drive of the trip back up to
Christchurch. Remember when I said that
maybe, just maybe we would get to see
this view in good [music] weather the
second time around?
Howdy. So, we just [music] pulled over.
This is Lake Pukaki, which is just a bit
south of Tekapo. We drove [music] on
this road like a week ago at this point,
probably even longer,
and it was when we had the horrible
weather, and I remember us saying how
insane this view would be if it was
sunny. [music] I think it's the bluest
water we've seen the whole trip.
>> [music]
>> Hello.
We're currently in [music] the home
garden of our Airbnb host, who we just
talked to it for like 30 minutes, and
she showed us every little bit of what
she's [music] planting. So, she's the
fruit gal, and her husband is the
vegetable guy, and we went into the
tomato greenhouse. And if you guys know
me, you know that tomatoes are my
favorite food of all time. What did she
do? She picked me one. She picked me
two, and she gave them to us. But, it
was probably one of, if not the, like,
coolest nicest conversation we've had so
far in New Zealand, where [music] of 10,
connecting with local, her being excited
that we're in New Zealand, us asking her
ton of questions. It was just so cute
[music] and pleasant. And then we gave
her some of our strawberries. So, we
traded produce, but I wish you could
smell this. Anyways, so they've lived
here since 1984, and she and [music] her
husband have planted all of this,
obviously. They they planted all of
these trees, and they planted them
[music] to attract the birds, which you
can
hear. But, it was just it was just the
cutest encounter.
>> [music]
>> Good morning. [music] There's the farm
fresh tomatoes you gave us. I just cut
it up. We're going to eat it.
>> [music]
>> In this cute spot for just coffee. We're
not doing food right now, but we've been
driving Christchurch
>> [music]
>> and today's our final Oh my god. Yeah,
our final big day.
We fly out tomorrow morning. We are back
in Christchurch after [music]
What about an hour? No, it's like a
2-hour drive from when we came to this
place on the places. It's a wood [music]
burning fire. And there's pizza.
Yeah. Yeah, so good. Squid and french
>> [music]
>> fries.
>> Actually, we're right outside of
Christchurch in Lyttelton. Feels like
Red Hook for New Yorkers today a little
bit where there's like ships [music]
and shipping containers out on the
water, but then really, really cool
spots like this. Yeah, it's like a cool
little enclave.
>> [music]
[music]
>> We noticed [music] pretty quickly after
getting to New Zealand that something in
us had relaxed. The pace of life slowed.
The people around us weren't rushing
anywhere. [music] The sounds of honking
cars faded away. It's been a long time
since my only obligation was to have fun
[music] and it made me feel like a kid
again. Happy to be there, present, and
exhausting myself outside in the sun.
And the people [music] disarmingly,
genuinely kind. Almost in a way that
catches you off guard when the hustle
and bustle of New York [music] City
becomes your norm. The stark contrast
between my busy daily life in New York
and the relaxed nature focused pace in
New Zealand didn't make me sad [music]
though. It reminded me that it's okay to
take a beat. It's okay not to rush past
every stranger on the sidewalk who is
walking only 90% of my ideal speed. I
came home a little softer and [music] I
think that's a good thing. New Zealand,
we will be back.
Super clean. No trash anywhere. Stave
taken over. This is Christchurch. Did I
even say that? I didn't in Christchurch.
You guys know this. I
I I I teed it up. All right, let's get
going.
What's up, Turtle Gang? Here we are in
our first hotel. Some raindrops.
Raindrop. Drop top.
Excellent.
I'm going to take my horse to the In 300
m, turn right onto Exeter Street. till I
can't no more.
Hello, bird.
Oh, he's so spunky.
I tried again.
Wait, hold on.
>> [laughter]
>> I'll tell you when.
3 2
Well, howdy there.
Woah!
Burning Man
Oh, yeah.
Why don't you listen to me, babe?